JOSE MARTOS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

TECH STACK

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, RWD JavaScript, ES6+, jQuery, Vue.js Jest, Node.js, Express, MongoDB

Webpack, Parcel, Gulp, Babel, ESlint, Prettier, PostCSS

Page optimization, SEO JIRA, Git(flow), Docker, Jenkins

COURSES

- React 16.8 (10h | 2019)
- Javascript testing practises and principles (5h | 2019)
- API design in Node.js (4h | 2019)
- Typescript 3 (5h | 2019)
- Photoshop CS5 (80h | 2012)
- Systems and networking (534h | 2006)

TOOLS

- VS Code, WebStorm, Sublime Text
- Invision, Zeplin, Avocode, Fireworks, Photoshop
- Sequel Pro, HeidiSQL, Compass

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: C1 | German: B1

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Trekking, Traveling, Reading, Photography, Martial arts

CONTACT

martosjosele@gmail.com Based in Munich 10.07.1987 – Málaga, Spain github.com/josemartos

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Developer with +9 years of experience. I am eager for new experiences, a creative problem solver, and fast learner. When working, I value politeness, code quality, sense of humour, team-work, reliability, and proactivity.

I am happy to live in a time with great tools and frameworks to assist developers in building applications better and faster. I am looking for a suitable position in a established company. Somewhere to share and acquire new ideas, thoughts and abilities.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

Front-end Developer

Pantaflix GmbH - Berlin (Mar 2017 - Sep 2018)

- Implemented a CMS tool for the customer care department using Vue.js, responsible for the set-up with Webpack and further development
- Responsible for the front-end on a CMS for filmmakers and consumers, using plain JavaScript and Twig
- Implemented new features on the main website, using jQuery and Node.js

Front-end Developer

Team2Venture GmbH - Berlin (Oct 2014 - Feb 2017)

- Participated in a CMS for external companies to handle freelancers and projects, using plain JavaScript and Scala templates
- Responsible for the development of a hybrid mobile app, using AngularJS
- Implemented new features on the main website, participating on a migration from Backbone and RequireJS to plain JavaScript and Browserify + Gulp

Full-stack Developer

Dreamsite - Madrid (Jun 2012 - Sep 2014)

- Developed +10 corporation websites using jQuery and PHP
- Integrated designs in Wordpress pages
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

Junior Full-stack Developer

Uniagro SL - Málaga (Jul 2009 - May 2012)

- Designed and developed +15 corporation websites using jQuery and PHP
- Designed logos and banners
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

EDUCATION

Senior Technician in Computer Applications Development (2007 - 2009) IES Pedro Espinosa, Antequera, Málaga